[
  {"id": 1, "question": "one, two, three, ______, five", "options": ["a. six", "b. four", "c. ten", "d. eight"], "correctAnswer": "b. four"},
  {"id": 2, "question": "My ______ is Christina.", "options": ["a. age", "b. number", "c. name", "d. friend"], "correctAnswer": "c. name"},
  {"id": 3, "question": "“What's your job?”\n“I'm a ______.”", "options": ["a. person", "b. teacher", "c. Peter", "d. student"], "correctAnswer": "b. teacher"},
  {"id": 4, "question": "“How are you?”\n“I'm ______, thank you.”", "options": ["a. fine", "b. seventeen", "c. hello", "d. tired"], "correctAnswer": "a. fine"},
  {"id": 5, "question": "“Where are you from?”\n“I'm from ______ .”", "options": ["a. American", "b. British", "c. Japan", "d. Canada"], "correctAnswer": "b. British"},
  {"id": 6, "question": "“Is he from China?”\n“Yes, ______ .”", "options": ["a. is he", "b. he is", "c. he's", "d. she is"], "correctAnswer": "b. he is"},
  {"id": 7, "question": "She is ______ married.", "options": ["a. not", "b. no", "c. the", "d. happily"], "correctAnswer": "a. not"},
  {"id": 8, "question": "Monday, Tuesday, ______, Thursday", "options": ["a. Sunday", "b. Wednesday", "c. Friday", "d. Saturday"], "correctAnswer": "b. Wednesday"},
  {"id": 9, "question": "“What's this?”\n“______ a book.”", "options": ["a. It", "b. This", "c. It's", "d. That"], "correctAnswer": "a. It"},
  {"id": 10, "question": "John and Mary ______ married.", "options": ["a. is", "b. are", "c. have", "d. were"], "correctAnswer": "b. are"},
  {"id": 11, "question": "nine, ten, ______, twelve", "options": ["a. eight", "b. eleven", "c. thirteen", "d. fifteen"], "correctAnswer": "b. eleven"},
  {"id": 12, "question": "name: names, person: people, man: ______.", "options": ["a. men", "b. mans", "c. mean", "d. men's"], "correctAnswer": "a. men"},
  {"id": 13, "question": "“How much is this?”\n“It's ______.”", "options": ["a. four dollars", "b. four kilos", "c. four years", "d. four cents"], "correctAnswer": "a. four dollars"},
  {"id": 14, "question": "“How old is she?”\n“ ______ fifteen years old.”", "options": ["a. She's", "b. Her", "c. He's", "d. I'm"], "correctAnswer": "a. She's"},
  {"id": 15, "question": "Please, come in and sit ______.", "options": ["a. up", "b. off", "c. down", "d. here"], "correctAnswer": "c. down"},
  {"id": 16, "question": "I ______ English.", "options": ["a. am like", "b. like", "c. do like", "d. speak"], "correctAnswer": "b. like"},
  {"id": 17, "question": "We ______ in Amsterdam.", "options": ["a. like", "b. do live", "c. live", "d. are"], "correctAnswer": "c. live"},
  {"id": 18, "question": "“What time is it?”\n“It's ______.”", "options": ["a. five years old", "b. eight o'clock", "c. six time", "d. half past eight"], "correctAnswer": "b. eight o'clock"},
  {"id": 19, "question": "February, March, ______, May", "options": ["a. June", "b. August", "c. April", "d. July"], "correctAnswer": "c. April"},
  {"id": 20, "question": "“______ is your favorite actor?”\n“Anthony Hopkins.”", "options": ["a. What", "b. How", "c. Who", "d. Why"], "correctAnswer": "c. Who"},
  {"id": 21, "question": "He's very ______.", "options": ["a. well", "b. student", "c. work", "d. tired"], "correctAnswer": "a. well"},
  {"id": 22, "question": "I ______ like rap music.", "options": ["a. not", "b. don't", "c. am not", "d. can't"], "correctAnswer": "b. don't"},
  {"id": 23, "question": "I have breakfast at eight o'clock in the ______.", "options": ["a. evening", "b. afternoon", "c. morning", "d. night"], "correctAnswer": "c. morning"},
  {"id": 24, "question": "“What ______ is your car?”\n“It's blue.”", "options": ["a. time", "b. color", "c. day", "d. make"], "correctAnswer": "b. color"},
  {"id": 25, "question": "“______ do you live?”\n“In Boston.”", "options": ["a. Where", "b. Who", "c. What", "d. When"], "correctAnswer": "a. Where"},
  {"id": 26, "question": "“What's ______ name?”\n“Elizabeth.”", "options": ["a. his", "b. she", "c. her", "d. its"], "correctAnswer": "c. her"},
  {"id": 27, "question": "I have a brother ______ two sisters.", "options": ["a. and", "b. but", "c. at", "d. with"], "correctAnswer": "a. and"},
  {"id": 28, "question": "Please ______ the door.", "options": ["a. close", "b. take", "c. stand", "d. open"], "correctAnswer": "a. close"},
  {"id": 29, "question": "I ______ in a bank.", "options": ["a. live", "b. work", "c. like", "d. study"], "correctAnswer": "b. work"},
  {"id": 30, "question": "In the dining room there is a table and six ______.", "options": ["a. gardens", "b. baths", "c. chairs", "d. plates"], "correctAnswer": "c. chairs"},
  {"id": 31, "question": "I play ______ on Saturdays.", "options": ["a. tennis", "b. dinner", "c. television", "d. chess"], "correctAnswer": "a. tennis"},
  {"id": 32, "question": "I ______ to bed at ten o'clock.", "options": ["a. go", "b. have", "c. do", "d. sleep"], "correctAnswer": "a. go"},
  {"id": 33, "question": "My book is ______ the table.", "options": ["a. in", "b. at", "c. on", "d. under"], "correctAnswer": "c. on"},
  {"id": 34, "question": "The Smiths ______ three children.", "options": ["a. are", "b. have", "c. has", "d. is"], "correctAnswer": "b. have"},
  {"id": 35, "question": "I ______ listening to the radio.", "options": ["a. is", "b. are", "c. am", "d. like"], "correctAnswer": "c. am"},
  {"id": 36, "question": "______ are you going on vacation?", "options": ["a. Where", "b. What", "c. Who", "d. When"], "correctAnswer": "a. Where"},
  {"id": 37, "question": "I'm ______ at home today.", "options": ["a. stay", "b. to stay", "c. staying", "d. going"], "correctAnswer": "c. staying"},
  {"id": 38, "question": "You go to the ______ to see a movie.", "options": ["a. movie theater", "b. theater", "c. opera", "d. park"], "correctAnswer": "a. movie theater"},
  {"id": 39, "question": "Go along First Street and ______ left on Baker Street.", "options": ["a. take", "b. turn", "c. go", "d. walk"], "correctAnswer": "b. turn"},
  {"id": 40, "question": "I like ______.", "options": ["a. read", "b. to reading", "c. reading", "d. to read"], "correctAnswer": "c. reading"}
]
